# CARLOS GERMÁN JOFRÉ

Full Stack Developer

Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina
jof.uncuyo@gmail.com
Phone: +54 9 11 2792 5467
Github: github.com/whoknowsi
LinkedIn: /in/carlos-jofre-830273210/
Portfolio: whoknows-portfolio.vercel.app

I am a computer science student at the University of Buenos Aires and a Full Stack Web Developer. I have a solid foundation in programming languages and I have worked on various web development projects using multiple libraries and frameworks.

### **Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- React Native
- Next.js
- Vue.js
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL / MariaDB
- Firebase / Google Cloud
- Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Git
- Jest / Cypress / Playwright

# **Experience**

### Freelance web developer

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

#### Currently working on ServicioLibre web app:

- Collaborating with a team to develop a service application that connects consumers with service providers.
- Designing and implementing key features of the application, ensuring they meet user needs and are scalable for future growth.
- Troubleshooting and resolving technical issues to ensure a seamless user experience.

### Web developer

Jul 2022 - Oct 2022

#### Responsibilities:

- Developed a virtual 360 tour using Three.js and WebGL.
- Added interactive hotspots to the tour for user engagement.
- Optimized loading and smooth navigation implementing a tile-based system that dynamically loads and renders the necessary tiles based on the user's position and zoom level.

### Frontend developer

Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

#### Responsibilities:

- Contributed to the development and maintenance of a visually appealing and user-friendly website for MaridajeClub's live product sales platform.
- Implemented the live video streaming system to enable customers to watch product demonstrations and make informed purchasing decisions.
- Collaborated with the frontend team to ensure efficient and effective development and deployment of new features and improvements to the platform.

### **Education**

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

University of Buenos Aires

2021 - Present

# **Licenses & Certifications**

Full Stack Open - University of Helsinki

Nov 2022

https://studies.cs.helsinki.fi/stats/api/certificate/fullstackopen/en/867a851012773dbe7db3d5d71c333a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1d

C1 Advanced - EF SET https://www.efset.org/cert/KR1a48

Jan 2023

# Languages

• Spanish: Native

• English: C1 Advanced